<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art alva</title>
    <link>https://artalva.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on art alva</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 20:42:52 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://artalva.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Weakness</title>
      <link>https://artalva.github.io/posts/weakness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 20:42:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artalva.github.io/posts/weakness/</guid>
      <description>I feel weak right now.
It’s been nearly two weeks since I came back from Poland. My purpose was to work. I was set on getting a job and starting an online business. This in order to have money and a stable income by the time I went back to Martyna. As of right now, I don’t have a job nor have I made a single step towards that online business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime and Punishment</title>
      <link>https://artalva.github.io/posts/crimeandpunishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 20:42:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artalva.github.io/posts/crimeandpunishment/</guid>
      <description>Crime and Punishment, one of the greatest novels of the 20th century, revolves around the theory of a greater man to whom everything is allowed, touching on the subjects of morals, religion, reality clashing against subjectivity and sentimentalism, and the consequences of all of these concepts in play with one another.
Morality is the main topic of the novel. Raskolnikov&amp;rsquo;s theory asks why are some people allowed certain actions and others not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timezone</title>
      <link>https://artalva.github.io/posts/timezone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 10:00:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artalva.github.io/posts/timezone/</guid>
      <description>Timezone is a region of the world that shares the same standard of time. Unlike said regions share the same timezone internally, Tina and I do not. Poland and Costa Rica don’t share a timezone, in fact they’re quite a few timezones away, totaling 8 hours of difference most of the year, and 7 during winter.
Naturally this is a tremendous problem for interacting with each other, right? If we both live a typical life, I will be asleep when she’s in school, then I’ll have work when she’s free in the afternoon, and finally I’ll be free when she’s already asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gynecologist</title>
      <link>https://artalva.github.io/posts/gynecologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 16:00:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artalva.github.io/posts/gynecologist/</guid>
      <description>Today I woke up thinking about Martina going to the gynecologist. I felt anxious and frustrated again that she has to do it. I had an idea that calmed me down; her going with me. This reduced my anxiety enormously. She’ll agree to it too, probably will like it and even prefer it. “Sounds great, right?” I thought, however, it made me wonder&amp;hellip; why? Why don’t I feel anxious if we go together, why do I feel that way to begin with?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>